dogmasoft.in 2018-09-22

# Dogmasoft

## Privacy Policy

Recharge any mobile, Recharge online, Recharge anytime

All sales of service are final and there will be no refund or exchange permitted. Please be advised that You are responsible for the Recharge for and all charges that result from those purchases. Dogma Soft Limited is not responsible for any purchase of Recharge for an incorrect account number.

However, in a case where a transaction has been completed by you on the Site, and money has been charged to your card or bank account but a Services  has not delivered within 24 hours of your completion of the transaction then you may inform us by sending us an email on  
support@dogmasoft.in or posting us a message. In such a scenario you will be entitled to a full refund. We request you to include in the email the following details - Recharge value, Transaction date and Order Number (    ) shall investigate the incident and if it is found that money was indeed charged to your card or bank account without delivery of service then you will be refunded the money within 7 working days from the date of the receipt of your email

###  INFORMATION COLLECT

We simply collect your information, to provide better and rich experience with your subsequent visits. For example, what kind of mobile recharge, you supposedly want, what kind of bus type you like to travel and what kind of deals or offers you like the most. We collect your information in two different ways.

###  Technical Information – The Information We Fetch

Whenever you use our service, our analytics fetches your technical information, like your browser, ip address, your operating system, and much other technically relevant information.

###  WHY WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE YOUR COLLECTION

We collect your personal information, to understand your personal behavior, and choices, so we can create better experience for you, whenever you visit our web portal and secondly, to offer you better deals and propagation than your ideal choice.

We collect your technical information, simply for the sake of improving our back-end technology, so we can give you quick and hassle free experience. And you always come back to use our service.

###  HOW TO ACCESS YOUR INFORMATION AND UPDATE IT.

We always provide an access point to your information whenever you use our services. So there is no need to worry about information access and updatation. But in any case, if you have any problem in accessing your own information, you can always contact us.

###  NO INFORMATION DISCOLOSURE POLICY TO THIRD-PARTIES

We don’t share any personal or confidential information to any third-party for commercial and personal profit. However, we use your information for our in-house projects to make better future products and services.

###  WE ARE 100% SECURED AND CERTIFIED

We are GeoTrust certified service, which guarantees your personal information is in safe hands, and 100% secured from any internet hack or data theft attacks. Though along with GeoTrust SSL certification, we have also employed many security checks to make leak-free system.

###  POLICY CHANGES

Our Privacy Policy may change every once in a while. Though, we make these changes on growing demand of consumer or to compile with Government or Industry guidelines, but we won't decrease your rights under this Privacy Policy without your voice being heard. We will post any changes in Privacy Policy over here on this page. So keep visiting this page, for getting regular updates on privacy policy.

This privacy policy sets out how  **Dogma Soft Ltd**  uses and protects any information that you give  **Dogma Soft Ltd**  when you use this website.

**Dogma Soft Ltd**  is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. 

**Dogma Soft Ltd**  may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. This policy is effective from 07-12-2013. 

**What we collect** : We may collect the following information: 

1\. Name and job title  
2\. Contact information including email address  
3\. demographic information such as postcode, preferences and interests  
4\. other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

**What we do with the information we gather**

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with a better service, and in particular for the following reasons:

1\. Internal record keeping.  
2\. We may use the information to improve our products and services.
